<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<USCode>
  <Title name="TITLE 4.—FLAG AND SEAL, SEAT OF GOVERNEMENT, AND THE STATES">
    <Section name="1. Flag; stripes and stars on.">The flag of the United States shall be thirteen horizontal stripes, alternate red and white; and the union of the flag shall be forty-eight stars, white in a blue field. (R.S. § 1791.) The flag of the United States shall be thirteen horizontal stripes, alternate red and white; and the union of the flag shall be forty-eight stars, white in a blue field. (R.S. § 1791.)</Section>
    <Section name="2. Same; additional stars.">On the admission of a new State into the Union, one star shall be added to the union of the flag; and such addition shall take effect on the fourth day of July then next succeeding such admission. (R.S. § 1792.) On the admission of a new State into the Union, one star shall be added to the union of the flag; and such addition shall take effect on the fourth day of July then next succeeding such admission. (R.S. § 1792.)</Section>
    <Section name="3. Use of flag for advertising purposes; mutilation of flag.">Any person who, within the District of Columbia, in any manner, for exhibition or display, shall place or cause to be placed any word, figure, mark, picture, design, drawing, or any advertisement of any nature upon any flag, standard, colors, or ensign of the United States of America; or shall expose or cause to be exposed to public view any such flag, standard, colors, or ensign upon which shall have been printed, painted, or otherwise placed, or to which shall be attached, appended, affixed, or annexed any word, figure, mark, picture, design, or drawing, or any advertisement of any nature; or who, within the District of Columbia, shall manufacture, sell, expose for sale or to public view, or give away or have in possession for sale or to be given away or for use for any purpose, any article or substance being an article of merchandise, or a receptacle for merchandise or article or thing for carrying or transporting merchandise, upon which shall have been printed, painted, attached, or otherwise placed a representation of any such flag, standard, colors, or ensign, to advertise, call attention to, decorate, mark, or distinguish the article or substance on which so placed; or who, within the District of Columbia, shall publicly mutilate, deface, defile, or defy, trample upon or cast contempt, either by word or act, upon any such flag, standard, colors, or ensign, shall be deemed guilty of a misdemeanor and shall be punished by a fine not exceeding $100 or by imprisonment for not more than thirty days, or both, in the discretion of the court. Any person who, within the District of Columbia, in any manner, for exhibition or display, shall place or cause to be placed any word, figure, mark, picture, design, drawing, or any advertisement of any nature upon any flag, standard, colors, or ensign of the United States of America; or shall expose or cause to be exposed to public view any such flag, standard, colors, or ensign upon which shall have been printed, painted, or otherwise placed, or to which shall be attached, appended, affixed, or annexed any word, figure, mark, picture, design, or drawing, or any advertisement of any nature; or who, within the District of Columbia, shall manufacture, sell, expose for sale or to public view, or give away or have in possession for sale or to be given away or for use for any purpose, any article or substance being an article of merchandise, or a receptacle for merchandise or article or thing for carrying or transporting merchandise, upon which shall have been printed, painted, attached, or otherwise placed a representation of any such flag, standard, colors, or ensign, to advertise, call attention to, decorate, mark, or distinguish the article or substance on which so placed; or who, within the District of Columbia, shall publicly mutilate, deface, defile, or defy, trample upon or cast contempt, either by word or act, upon any such flag, standard, colors, or ensign, shall be deemed guilty of a misdemeanor and shall be punished by a fine not exceeding $100 or by imprisonment for not more than thirty days, or both, in the discretion of the court.</Section>
    <Section name="4. Seal of United States.">The seal heretofore used by the United States in Congress assembled is declared to be the seal of the United States. (R.S. § 1793.)</Section>
    <Section name="5. Same; custody and use of.">The Secretary of State shall have the custody and charge of such seal, and shall make out and record, and shall affix the same to, all civil commissions for officers of the United States, to be appointed by the President, by and with the advice and consent of the Senate, or by the President alone. But the seal shall not be affixed to any commission before the same has been signed by the President of the United States, nor to any other instrument, without the special warrant of the President therefor. (R.S. §§ 203, 1794.)</Section>
    <Section name="6. Permanent seat of government.">All that part of the territory of the United States included within the present limits of the District of Columbia shall be the permanent seat of government of the United States. (R.S. § 1795.)</Section>
    <Section name="7. Public offices; at seat of government.">All offices attached to the seat of government shall be exercised in the District of Columbia, and not elsewhere, except as otherwise expressly provided by law. (R.S. § 1796.)</Section>
    <Section name="8. Same; removal from seat of government.">In case of the prevalence of a contagious or epidemic disease at the seat of government, the President may permit and direct the removal of any or all the public offices to such other place or places as he shall deem most safe and convenient for conducting the public business. (R.S. § 1797.)</Section>
    <Section name="9. Oath by members of legislatures and officers.">Every member of a State legislature, and every executive and judicial officer of a State, shall, before he proceeds to execute the duties of his office, take an oath in the following form, to wit: “I, A. B., do solemnly swear that I will support the Constitution of the United States.” (R.S. § 1836.)</Section>
    <Section name="10. Same; by whom administered.">Such oath may be administered by any person who, by the law of the State, is authorized to administer the oath of office; and the person so administering such oath shall cause a record or certificate thereof to be made in the same manner as, by the law of the State, he is directed to record or certify the oath of office. (R.S. § 1837.)</Section>
    <Section name="11. Assent to purchase of lands for forts.">The President of the United States is authorized to procure the assent of the legislature of any State, within which any purchase of land has been made for the erection of forts, magazines, arsenals, dockyards, and other needful buildings, without such consent having been obtained. (R.S. § 1838.)</Section>
  </Title>
</USCode>
