<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<USCode>
    <Title name="TITLE 2.—THE CONGRESS">
        <Chapter name="Chapter 1.—ELECTION OF SENATORS AND REPRESENTATIVES.">
            <Section name="1. Time for election of Senators.">At the regular election held in any State next preceding the expiration of the term for which any Senator was elected to represent such State in Congress, at which election a Representative to Congress is regularly by law to be chosen, a United States Senator from said State shall be elected by the people thereof for the term commencing on the 4th day of March next thereafter. (June 4, 1914, c. 103, § 1, 38 Stat. 384.)</Section>
            <Section name="2. Number and apportionment of Representatives.">The House of Representatives shall be composed of four hundred and thirty-five Members, to be apportioned among the several States as follows:</Section>
            <Section name="4. Additional Representatives at large.">In case of an increase in the number of Representatives in any State under this apportionment, such additional Representative or Representatives shall be elected by the State at large and the other Representatives by the districts prescribed by law on August 8, 1911, until such State shall be redistricted in the manner provided by the laws thereof and in accordance with the rules enumerated in section 3. If there be no change in the number of Representatives from a State, the Representatives thereof shall be elected from the districts prescribed by law on August 8, 1911, until such State shall be redistricted as herein prescribed. (Aug. 8, 1911, c. 5, § 4, 37 Stat. 14.)</Section>
            <Section name="5. Nominations for Representatives at large.">Candidates for Representative or Representatives to be elected at large in any State shall be nominated in the same manner as candidates for governor, unless otherwise provided by the laws of such State. (Aug. 8, 1911, c. 5, § 5, 37 Stat. 15.)</Section>
            <Section name="6. Reduction of representation.">Should any State deny or abridge the right of any of the male inhabitants thereof, being twenty-one years of age, and citizens of the United States, to vote at any election named in the amendment to the Constitution, article 14, section 2, except for participation in rebellion or other crime, the number of Representatives apportioned to such State shall be reduced in the proportion which the number of such male citizens shall have to the whole number of male citizens twenty-one years of age in such State. (R.S. § 22.)</Section>
            <Section name="7. Time of election.">The Tuesday next after the 1st Monday in November, in every even numbered year, is established as the day for the election, in each of the States and Territories of the United States, of Representatives and Delegates to Congress commencing on the 4th day of March next thereafter. This section shall not apply to any State that has not yet changed its day of election, and whose constitution must be amended in order to effect a change in the day of the election of State officers in said State. (R.S. § 25; Mar. 3, 1875, c. 130, § 6, 18 Stat. 400.)</Section>
            <Section name="8. Vacancies.">The time for holding elections in any State, District, or Territory for a Representative or Delegate to fill a vacancy, whether such vacancy is caused by a failure to elect at the time prescribed by law, or by the death, resignation, or incapacity of a person elected, may be prescribed by the laws of the several States and Territories respectively. (R.S. § 26.)</Section>
            <Section name="9. Voting for Representatives.">All votes for Representatives in Congress must be by written or printed ballot, or voting machine the use of which has been duly authorized by the State law; and all votes received or recorded contrary to this section shall be of no effect. (R.S. § 27; Feb. 14, 1899, c. 154, 30 Stat. 836.)</Section>
            <Section name="21. Oath of Senators.">The oath of office shall be administered by the President of the Senate to each Senator who shall be elected, previous to his taking his seat. (R.S. § 28.)</Section>
            <Section name="22. Oath of President of Senate.">When a President of the Senate has not taken the oath of office, it shall be administered to him by any Member of the Senate. (R.S. § 29.)</Section>
            <Section name="23. Presiding officer of Senate may administer oaths.">The presiding officer, for the time being, of the Senate of the United States, shall have power to administer all oaths and affirmations that are or may be required by the Constitution, or by law, to be taken by any Senator, officer of the Senate, witness, or other person, in respect to any matter within the jurisdiction of the Senate. (Apr. 18, 1876, c. 60, § 1, 19 Stat. 34.)</Section>
            <Section name="24. Secretary of Senate or Chief Clerk may administer oaths.">The Secretary of the Senate, and the Chief Clerk thereof, shall, respectively, have power to administer any oath or affirmation required by law, or by the rules or orders of the Senate, to be taken by any officer of the Senate, and to any witness produced before it. (Apr. 18, 1876, c. 66, § 2, 19 Stat. 34.)</Section>
            <Section name="25. Oath of Speaker, Members, and Delegates.">At the first session of Congress after every general election of Representatives, the oath of office shall be administered by any Member of the House of Representatives to the Speaker; and by the Speaker to all the Members and Delegates present, and to the Clerk, previous to entering on any other business; and to the Members and Delegates who afterward appear, previous to their taking their seats. (R.S. § 30.)</Section>
            <Section name="26. Roll of Representatives-elect.">Before the first meeting of each Congress the Clerk of the next preceding House of Representatives shall make a roll of the Representatives-elect, and place thereon the names of those persons, and of such persons only, whose credentials show that they were regularly elected in accordance with the laws of their States respectively, or the laws of the United States. In case of a vacancy in the office of Clerk of the House of Representatives, or of the absence or inability of the Clerk to discharge the duties imposed on him by law or custom relative to the preparation of the roll of Representatives or the organization of the House, those duties shall devolve on the Sergeant at Arms of the next preceding House of Representatives. In case of vacancies in the offices of both the Clerk and the Sergeant at Arms, or of the absence or inability of both to act, the duties of the Clerk relative to the preparation of the roll of the House of Representatives or the organization of the House shall be performed by the Doorkeeper of the next preceding House of Representatives. (R.S. §§ 31, 32, 33.)</Section>
            <Section name="27. Change of place of meeting.">Whenever Congress is about to convene, and from the prevalence of contagious sickness, or the existence of other circumstances, it would, in the opinion of the President, be hazardous to the lives or health of the members to meet at the seat of Government, the President is authorized, by proclamation, to convene Congress at such other place as he may judge proper. (R.S. § 34.)</Section>
        </Chapter>
        <Chapter name="Chapter 3.—COMPENSATION OF MEMBERS.">
            <Section name="31. Compensation of Members of Congress.">The compensation of the Speaker of the House of Representatives shall be at the rate of $15,000 per annum, and the compensation of Senators, Representatives in Congress, Delegates from Territories, Resident Commissioner from Porto Rico, and Resident Commissioners from the Philippine Islands shall be at the rate of $10,000 per annum each. (Mar. 4, 1925, c. 549, § 4, 43 Stat. 1301.)</Section>
            <Section name="32. Compensation of President of Senate.">Whenever there is no Vice President, the President of the Senate for the time being is entitled to the compensation provided by law for the Vice President. (R.S. § 36.)</Section>
            <Section name="33. Senators’ salaries payable monthly.">Senators elected, whose term of office begins on the 4th day of March, and whose credentials in due form of law shall have been presented in the Senate, but who have had no opportunity to be qualified, may receive their compensation monthly, from the beginning of their term, until there shall be a session of the Senate. (Mar. 3, 1883, c. 143, 22 Stat. 632.)</Section>
            <Section name="34. Representatives’ salaries payable monthly.">Representatives and Delegates elect to Congress, whose credentials in due form of law have been duly filed with the Clerk of the House of Representatives, in accordance with the provisions of section 20 of this title, may receive their compensation monthly, from the beginning of their term until the beginning of the first session of each Congress, upon a certificate in the form now in use to be signed by the Clerk of the House, which certificate shall have the like force and effect as is given to the certificate of the Speaker. (R.S. § 38; Mar. 3, 1875, c. 130, § 1, 18 Stat. 389.)</Section>
            <Section name="35. Salaries payable monthly after taking oath.">Each Member and Delegate, after he has taken and subscribed the required oath, is entitled to receive his salary at the end of each month. (R.S. § 39.)</Section>
            <Section name="36. Salaries of Senators appointed or elected to fill vacancies.">Salaries of Senators appointed to fill vacancies in the Senate shall commence on the day of their appointment and continue until their successors are elected and qualified; and salaries of Senators elected to fill vacancies in the Senate shall commence on the day they qualify: Provided, That where no appointments have been made to fill such vacancies, the salaries of Senators elected to fill such vacancies shall commence on the day following their election. (Feb. 10, 1923, c. 68, 42 Stat. 1225.)</Section>
            <Section name="37. Salaries of Representatives, Delegates, and Resident Commissioners elected for unexpired terms.">The salaries of Representatives in Congress, Delegates from Territories, and Resident Commissioners, elected for unexpired terms, shall commence on the date of their election and not before. (R.S. § 51; July 10, 1914, c. 141, § 1, 38 Stat. 458.)</Section>
            <Section name="38. Pay of Member dying after commencement of Congress.">When any person who has been elected a Member of or Delegate in Congress dies after the commencement of the Congress to which he has been elected, his salary shall be computed and paid to his widow, or, if no widow survive him, to his heirs at law, for the period that has elapsed from the commencement of such Congress, or from the last payment received by him to the time of his death, at the rate of $10,000 a year, with any mileage remaining due for actually going to or returning from any session of Congress. Salaries so allowed shall be computed and paid in all cases, for a period of not less than three months from the commencement of the Congress. (R.S. §§ 49, 50; Jan. 20, 1874, c. 11, 18 Stat. 4.)</Section>
            <Section name="39. Deductions for absence.">The Secretary of the Senate and Sergeant at Arms of the House, respectively, shall deduct from the monthly payments of each Member or Delegate the amount of his salary for each day that he has been absent from the Senate or House, respectively, unless such Member or Delegate assigns as the reason for such absence the sickness of himself or of some member of his family. (R.S. § 40.)</Section>
            <Section name="40. Deductions for withdrawal.">When any Member or Delegate withdraws from his seat and does not return before the adjournment of Congress, he shall, in addition to the sum deducted for each day, forfeit a sum equal to the amount which would have been allowed by law for his mileage in returning home; and such sum shall be deducted from his compensation, unless the withdrawal is with the leave of the Senate or House of Representatives respectively. (R.S. § 41.)</Section>
            <Section name="41. Newspapers.">No Member or Delegate is entitled to any allowance for newspapers. (R.S. § 43.)</Section>
            <Section name="42. Postage.">No compensation or allowance shall be made to Senators, Representatives, or Delegates on account of postage. (R.S. § 44.)</Section>
            <Section name="43. Mileage of Senators, Representatives, and Delegates.">Each Senator, Representative, and Delegate shall receive mileage at the rate of 20 cents per mile, to be estimated by the nearest route usually traveled in going to and returning from each regular session. (July 28, 1866, c. 290, § 17, 14 Stat. 323; Jan. 20, 1874, c. 11, 18 Stat. 4.)</Section>
            <Section name="44. Mileage allowance to Delegate from Alaska.">The Delegate from Alaska, in lieu of all other allowances, shall, in addition to his salary, receive the sum of $1,500 per annum, which shall cover all mileage and other expenses, except stationery allowance and compensation for clerk hire. (May 7, 1906, c. 2083, § 1, 34 Stat. 170.)</Section>
            <Section name="45. Mileage allowance to Resident Commissioners from Philippine Islands.">Each of the Resident Commissioners from the Philippine Islands shall, in addition to the salary allowed by law, receive $2,000 per annum, in lieu of mileage. (July 1, 1902, c. 1369, § 8, 32 Stat. 694; Aug. 29, 1916, c. 416, § 20, 39 Stat. 552.)</Section>
            <Section name="46. Mileage allowance to Resident Commissioner from Porto Rico.">The Resident Commissioner from Porto Rico shall be allowed the sum of $500 as mileage for each session of the House of Representatives. (Mar. 2, 1917, c. 145, § 10, 39 Stat. 963.)</Section>
            <Section name="47. Mode of payment.">The compensation of Members and Delegates shall be passed as public accounts, and paid out of the public Treasury. (R.S. § 46.)</Section>
            <Section name="48. Certification of salary and mileage accounts.">Salary and mileage accounts of Senators shall be certified by the President of the Senate, and those of Representatives and Delegates by the Speaker of the House of Representatives; and such certificates shall be conclusive upon all the departments and officers of the Government. (R.S. §§ 47, 48; July 28, 1866, c. 290, § 17, 14 Stat. 323; Jan. 20, 1874, c. 11, 18 Stat. 4.)</Section>
            <Section name="49. Certificate of salary during recess.">The Clerk of the House of Representatives is authorized and directed to sign, during the recess of Congress after the first session and until the first day of the second session, the certificates for the monthly compensation of Members and Delegates in Congress, which certificate shall be in the form in use on August 15, 1870, and shall have the like force and effect as is given to the certificate of the Speaker. (Aug. 15, 1870, c. 287, § 1, 16 Stat. 305.)</Section>
            <Section name="50. Substitute to sign certificates for salary and accounts.">The Speaker is authorized to designate from time to time someone from among those appointed by him and appropriated for and employed in his office, whose duty it shall be under the direction of the Speaker to sign in his name and for him all certificates required by section 48 of this title for salary and accounts for traveling expenses in going to and returning from Congress of Representatives and Delegates. (Nov. 12, 1903, No. 1, 33 Stat. 1.)</Section>
            <Section name="51. Monuments to deceased Senators or Members of House.">Whenever any deceased Senator or Member of the House of Representatives shall be actually interred in the Congressional Cemetery, so called, it shall be the duty of the Sergeant at Arms of the Senate, in the case of a Senator, and of the Sergeant at Arms of the House of Representatives, in the case of a Member of the House, to have a monument erected, of granite, with suitable inscriptions, and the cost of the same shall be a charge upon and paid out either from the contingent funds of the Senate or of the House of Representatives, to whichever the deceased may have belonged, and any existing omissions of monuments or inscriptions, as aforesaid, are directed and authorized to be supplied in like manner. (May 23, 1870, c. 103, 16 Stat. 54.)</Section>
        </Chapter>
        <Chapter name="Chapter 4.—OFFICERS AND EMPLOYEES OF SENATE AND HOUSE OF REPRESENTATIVES.">
            <Section name="61. Limit on rate of compensation of officers and employees of Senate.">No officer or employee of the Senate shall receive pay for any services performed by him at any rate higher than that provided for the office or employment to which he has been regularly appointed. (Aug. 5, 1882, c. 390, § 1, 22 Stat. 270.)</Section>
            <Section name="62. Limitation on compensation of Sergeant at Arms and Doorkeeper of Senate.">The Sergeant at Arms and Doorkeeper of the Senate shall receive, directly or indirectly, no fees or other compensation or emolument whatever for performing the duties of the office, or in connection therewith, other than the salary prescribed by law. (June 20, 1874, c. 328, § 1, 18 Stat. 85; Mar. 3, 1875, c. 129, § 1, 18 Stat. 344.)</Section>
            <Section name="63. Duties of Senate Doorkeeper.">The Doorkeeper of the Senate shall perform the usual services pertaining to his office during the session of Congress, and shall in the recess, under the direction of the Secretary of the Senate, take care of the apartments occupied by the Senate. (R.S. § 73.)</Section>
            <Section name="64. Secretary of Senate a disbursing officer.">The moneys appropriated for the compensation of Members and officers, and for the contingent expenses of the Senate, shall be paid at the Treasury, on requisitions drawn by the Secretary of the Senate, and shall be kept, disbursed, and accounted for by him according to law, and the Secretary shall be deemed a disbursing officer. (R.S. § 56.)</Section>
            <Section name="65. Bond of Secretary of Senate.">The Secretary of the Senate shall, within thirty days after entering upon the duties of his office, and before making any requisition upon the Treasury to draw any portion of the moneys appropriated for the compensation of Members and officers or the contingent expenses of the Senate, give a bond to the United States, with one or more sureties, to be approved by the Secretary of the Treasury, in the penal sum of $20,000, with condition for the faithful application and disbursement of such funds as may be drawn by him from the Treasury as disbursing officer of the Senate, which bond shall be deposited in the office of the Secretary of the Treasury. (R.S. §§ 57, 59; May 2, 1895, c. 177, § 5, 28 Stat. 807.)</Section>
            <Section name="66. Fiscal year for adjustment of accounts of Secretary of Senate.">The fiscal year for the adjustment of the accounts of the Secretary of the Senate, for compensation and traveling expenses of Senators, shall extend to and include the third day of July. (R.S. § 237; Oct. 1, 1890, c. 1256, § 9, 26 Stat. 646.)</Section>
            <Section name="67. Clerks to Senators elect.">Senators elected, whose term of office begins on the fourth day of March, and whose credentials in due form of law shall have been presented to the Senate, or filed with the Secretary, but who have not been qualified, are authorized to appoint a clerk to serve from the date of the commencement of their terms, respectively, whose compensation shall be paid out of the appropriation for clerks to Senators who are not chairmen of committees. (Mar. 2, 1895, c. 177, § 1, 28 Stat. 766; Feb. 20, 1923, c. 98, 42 Stat. 1266.)</Section>
            <Section name="68. Payments from contingent fund of Senate.">No payment shall be made from the contingent fund of the Senate unless sanctioned by the Committee to Audit and Control the Contingent Expenses of the Senate. Payments made upon vouchers approved by said Committee shall be deemed, held, and taken, and are hereby declared to be conclusive upon all the departments and officers of the Government: Provided, That no payment shall be made from said contingent fund as additional salary or compensation to any officer or employee of the Senate. (Oct. 2, 1888, c. 1069, § 1, 25 Stat. 546.)</Section>
            <Section name="69. Same; for expenses of committees.">When any duty is imposed upon a committee of the Senate involving expenses which are ordered to be paid out of the contingent fund of the Senate, upon vouchers to be approved by the chairman of the committee charged with such duty, the receipt of the chairman of such committee for any sum paid to him or his order out of said contingent fund by the Secretary of the Senate shall be taken and passed by the General Accounting Office as a full and sufficient voucher; but it shall be the duty of such chairman, as soon as practicable, to furnish vouchers in detail for the disbursement of such moneys to the Secretary of the Senate, who shall file them with the General Accounting Office. (Mar. 3, 1879, c. 183, § 1, 20 Stat. 419.)</Section>
            <Section name="70. Same; Senate resolutions for payment for clerical and messenger service.">All Senate resolutions passed prior to July 1, 1914, authorizing the payment for clerical and messenger services from the contingent fund of the Senate are hereby repealed. (July 16, 1914, c. 141, § 1, 38 Stat. 456.)</Section>
            <Section name="71. Motor equipment for Senate.">The Secretary of War is authorized in his discretion to transfer without charge to the Sergeant at Arms of the United States Senate such motor equipment as is suitable to the needs of the Senate and which is no longer required for the use of the War Department. (July 11, 1919, c. 6, § 1, 41 Stat. 57.)</Section>
            <Section name="72. Committee employees after termination of Congress.">Appropriations for committee employees shall not be available for the payment of any clerk or assistant clerk to a committee who does not, after the termination of the Congress during which he was appointed, perform his duties under the direction of the Clerk of the House. This provision shall not apply to the Committee on Accounts. (Mar. 4, 1925, c. 549, § 1, 43 Stat. 1291.)</Section>
            <Section name="73. Clerk for minority members of Committee on Ways and Means.">The position of a clerk for the minority members of the Committee on Ways and Means is hereby established at such rate of compensation as Congress may from time to time appropriate and incumbents thereof shall be appointed by and be subject to the direction of the ranking minority member of that committee. During the period between the expiration of a Congress and the election of the members of the Committee on Ways and Means at the succeeding Congress such clerk shall be appointed by and be subject to the direction of that ranking minority member of the committee of the expiring Congress who is also a member elect of the succeeding Congress. (Mar. 4, 1925, c. 549, § 1, 43 Stat. 1292.)</Section>
            <Section name="74. Clerk hire, Members, Delegates, and Resident Commissioners.">The clerk hire for clerks necessarily employed by each Member, Delegate, and Resident Commissioner, in the discharge of his official and representative duties, shall be at the rate of $4,000 per annum and shall be paid in accordance with section 92 of this title, but no person shall receive a salary from such clerk hire at a rate in excess of $3,300 per annum. (R.S. §§ 56, 54; Mar. 3, 1893, No. 21, 27 Stat. 757; July 16, 1914, c. 141, §§ 1, 6, 38 Stat. 454, 509; Mar. 4, 1915, c. 141, §§ 1, 6, 38 Stat. 997, 1049; May 24, 1924, c. 183, § 1, 43 Stat. 149; June 7, 1924, c. 303, § 1, 43, Stat. 581; Mar. 4, 1925,c. 549, § 1, 43 Stat. 1286.)</Section>
            <Section name="75. Bond of Clerk of House of Representatives.">The Clerk of the House of Representatives shall, within thirty days after entering upon the duties of his office, and before making any requisition upon the Treasury to draw any portion of the moneys appropriated for the contingent expenses of the House, give a bond to the United States, with one or more sureties, to be approved by the Secretary of the Treasury, in the penal sum of $20,000, with condition for the faithful application and disbursement of such portions of the contingent fund of the House as shall come into his hands, which bond shall be deposited in the office of the Secretary of the Treasury. (R.S. §§ 58, 59; Mar. 2, 1895, c. 177, § 5, 28 Stat. 807.)</Section>
            <Section name="76. Duties of Doorkeeper of House of Representatives.">The Doorkeeper of the House of Representatives shall perform the usual services pertaining to his office during the session of Congress, and shall in the recess, under the direction of the Clerk of the House of Representatives, take care of the apartments occupied by the House of Representatives. (R.S. § 73.)</Section>
            <Section name="77. Sergeant at Arms of House of Representatives; additional compensation.">The Sergeant at Arms of the House of Representatives shall receive, directly or indirectly, no fees or other compensation or emolument whatever for performing the duties of the office, or in connection therewith, otherwise than the salary prescribed by law. (June 20, 1874, c. 328, § 1, 18 Stat. 87; Mar. 3, 1875, c. 129, § 1, 18 Stat. 346.)</Section>
            <Section name="78. Same; duties.">It shall be the duty of the Sergeant at Arms of the House of Representatives to attend the House during its sittings, to maintain order under the direction of the Speaker, and, pending the election of a Speaker or Speaker pro tempore, under the direction of the Clerk, execute the commands of the House and all processes issued by authority thereof, directed to him by the Speaker, keep the accounts for the pay and mileage of Members and Delegates, and pay them as provided by law. (Oct. 1, 1890, c. 1256, § 1, 26 Stat. 645.)</Section>
            <Section name="79. Same; symbol of office.">The symbol of his office shall be the mace, which shall be borne by him while enforcing order on the floor. (Oct. 1, 1890, c. 1256, § 2, 26 Stat. 645.)</Section>
            <Section name="80. Same; disbursement of compensation of Members and Delegates.">The moneys which have been, or may be, appropriated for the compensation and mileage of Members and Delegates shall be paid at the Treasury on requisitions drawn by the Sergeant at Arms of the House of Representatives, and shall be kept, disbursed, and accounted for by him according to law, and he shall be a disbursing officer, but he shall not be entitled to any compensation additional to the salary fixed by law. (Oct. 1, 1890, c. 1256, § 3, 26 Stat. 645.)</Section>
            <Section name="81. Same; fiscal year for adjustment of accounts.">The fiscal year for the adjustment of the accounts of the Sergeant at Arms of the House of Representatives for compensation and mileage of Members and Delegates shall extend to and include the 3d day of July. (R.S. § 237; Oct. 1, 1890, c. 1256, § 9, 26 Stat. 646.)</Section>
            <Section name="82. Same; bond.">The Sergeant at Arms shall, within twenty days after entering upon the duties of his office, and before receiving any portion of the moneys appropriated for the compensation or mileage of Members and Delegates, give a bond to the United States, with two or more sureties, to be approved by the Secretary of the Treasury in the sum of $50,000, with condition for the proper discharge of the duties of his office, and the faithful keeping, application, and disbursement of such moneys as may be drawn from the Treasury and paid to him as disbursing officer of the United States, and shall, from time to time, renew his official bond as the Secretary of the Treasury shall direct. No Member of Congress shall be approved as surety on such bond. The bond given pursuant to this section shall be deposited in the office of the Secretary of the Treasury. (Oct. 1, 1890, c. 1256, §§ 4, 5, 26 Stat. 616; Mar. 2, 1895, c. 177, § 5, 28 Stat. 807.)</Section>
            <Section name="83. Same; tenure of office.">Any person duly elected and qualified as Sergeant-at-Arms of the House of Representatives shall continue in said office until his successor is chosen and qualified, subject, however, to removal by the House of Representatives. (Oct. 1, 1890, c. 1256, § 6, 26 Stat. 646.)</Section>
            <Section name="84. Same; statement of disbursements.">The Sergeant-at-Arms of the House of Representatives shall prepare and submit to the House of Representatives, at the commencement of each regular session of Congress, a statement in writing exhibiting the several sums drawn by him pursuant to sections 78 and 80 of this title, the application and disbursement of the same, and the balance, if any, remaining in his hands. (Oct. 1, 1890, c. 1256, § 7, 26 Stat. 646.)</Section>
            <Section name="85. Performance of duties by employees of House.">Employees of the House of Representatives under the Clerk, Sergeant-at-Arms, Doorkeeper, and Postmaster shall only be assigned to and engaged upon the duties of the positions to which they are appointed and for which compensation is provided; except that in cases of emergency or congestion of public business incident to the close of a session of Congress or other like cause an employee or employees may be assigned or required to aid in the discharge of the duties of any other employee or employees, and in the discretion of the Doorkeeper not more than one folder may, if necessary, be assigned to do clerical work under the direction of the foreman of the folding room; but all assignments made hereunder shall be without additional compensation and shall not constitute the basis of a claim therefor. (Mar. 3, 1901, c. 830, § 1, 31 Stat. 968.)</Section>
            <Section name="86. Division of salaries of employees of House of Representatives.">It shall not be lawful to appoint or employ in any position under the House of Representatives more than one person at any one time, or to require or permit any such person to divide with another any portion of his salary or compensation while so employed. (Mar. 3, 1901, c. 830, § 1, 31 Stat. 968.)</Section>
            <Section name="87. Subletting of duties of employees of House of Representatives forbidden.">It shall not be lawful to require or permit any person in the employ of the House of Representatives to sublet to another the discharge of any portion of the duties of the position to which he is appointed. (Mar. 3, 1901, c. 830, § 1, 31 Stat. 968.)</Section>
            <Section name="88. Limit of age of pages in House of Representatives.">No person shall be appointed or employed as a page in the service of the House of Representatives who is under twelve years or more than eighteen years of age; but this provision shall not apply to chief pages, riding pages, and telephone pages. (Mar. 3, 1901, c. 830, § 1, 31 Stat. 968.)</Section>
            <Section name="89. Certificates to pay rolls of employees in House of Representatives.">The Clerk, Sergeant-at-Arms, Doorkeeper, and Postmaster of the House of Representatives shall make certificate each month to their respective pay rolls, stating whether the persons named in such pay rolls and employed in their respective departments have been actually present at their respective places of duty and have actually performed the services for which compensation is provided in said pay rolls, and in each case where a person carried on such pay roll has been absent and has not performed the services in whole or in part for which payment is proposed, the reason for such absence and for such nonperformance of services shall be stated. (Mar. 3, 1901, c. 830, § 1, 31 Stat. 968.)</Section>
            <Section name="90. Removal from office of employees of House of Representatives.">The violation of any of the provisions of sections 85 to 89 of this title shall, upon ascertainment thereof, be deemed to be cause for removal from office. (Mar. 3, 1901, c. 830, § 1, 31 Stat. 968.)</Section>
            <Section name="91. Inquiry by Committee on Accounts of House of Representatives.">It shall be the duty of the Committee on Accounts of the House of Representatives from time to time to inquire into the enforcement or violation of any of the provisions of sections 85 to 90 of this title; and for this purpose they are authorized to send for persons and papers, and to administer oaths; and they shall report to the House at least once every session their compliance with the duty herein imposed. (Mar. 3, 1901, c. 830, § 1, 31 Stat. 968.)</Section>
            <Section name="92. Payment of appropriations for clerk hire for Members, Delegates, and Resident Commissioners.">Appropriations made by Congress for clerk hire for Members, Delegates, and Resident Commissioners shall be paid by the Clerk of the House of Representatives to one or two persons to be designated by each Member, Delegate, or Resident Commissioner, the names of such persons to be placed upon the roll of employees of the House of Representatives, together with the amount to be paid each; and Representatives, Delegates, and Resident Commissioners elect to Congress shall likewise be entitled to make such designations: Provided, That such persons shall be subject to removal at any time by such Member, Delegate, or Resident Commissioner with or without cause. (Jan. 25, 1923, c. 43, 42 Stat. 1217.)</Section>
            <Section name="93. Time of beginning of compensation of clerks to committees of House of Representatives paid during session only.">The pay of the clerks to committees of the House of Representatives which have been or may be authorized by the House, who are paid during the session only shall begin from the time such clerks entered upon the discharge of their duties, which shall be ascertained and evidenced by the certificate of the chairman of the several committees employing clerks for the session only. (June 28, 1886, No. 15, 24 Stat. 312.)</Section>
            <Section name="94. Appointment, duties, and removal of janitors to committees of House of Representatives.">Janitors to committees of the House of Representatives shall be appointed by the chairmen, respectively, of said committees, and shall perform under the direction of the Doorkeeper all of the duties required of messengers detailed to said committees by the Doorkeeper, and shall be subject to removal by the Doorkeeper at any time after the termination of the Congress during which they were appointed. (Mar. 4, 1925, c. 549, § 1, 43 Stat. 1291.)</Section>
            <Section name="95. Payments from contingent fund of House of Representatives.">No payment shall be made from the contingent fund of the House of Representatives unless sanctioned by the Committee on Accounts of the House of Representatives. Payments from the contingent fund made upon vouchers approved by said committee shall be deemed, held, and taken, and are hereby declared to be conclusive upon all the departments and officers of the Government. No payment shall be made from said contingent fund as additional salary or compensation to any officer or employee of the House of Representatives. (Oct. 2, 1888, c. 1069, § 1, 25 Stat. 546; Mar. 4, 1911, c. 240, 36 Stat. 1318.)</Section>
            <Section name="96. Payment from moneys of House of Representatives of certain bills.">It shall be unlawful for the Clerk of the House to pay out of any moneys of the House of Representatives any bills for laundry, furniture, supplies, or utensils used in the barber shops of the House Office Building or the House side of the Capitol. (July 16, 1914, c. 141, § 1, 38 Stat. 402.)</Section>
            <Section name="97. Temporary committee on accounts of House of Representatives.">The Speaker of the House of Representatives of each Congress shall, before the termination of the last session of each Congress, appoint, from the Representatives-elect, a temporary committee on accounts, of three members, which said committee on accounts shall have the same powers and perform the same duties in reference to payments made from the contingent fund of the House of Representatives of the next Congress as are authorized by law and the rules of the preceding House of Representatives. Said temporary committee on accounts shall begin to exercise its powers immediately upon the termination of the previous Congress, and shall continue to exercise and discharge said duties until after the meeting and organization of the House of Representatives of the succeeding Congress, and until the appointment of the regular committee on accounts. All payments made out of the contingent fund of the House of Representatives upon vouchers approved by said temporary committee on accounts shall be deemed, held, and taken, and are hereby declared to be conclusive upon all the departments and auditing officers of the Government. (Mar. 2, 1895, c. 177, § 1, 28 Stat. 768.)</Section>
            <Section name="98. Contracts for horses for service of House of Representatives.">In all contracts made for service for the House of Representatives involving the employment of horses, the expense of keeping such horses shall be covered by the contract; and no money appropriated for contingent or other expenses of the House of Representatives shall be expended for stables or forage. (Mar. 3, 1883, c. 300, 23 Stat. 512.)</Section>
            <Section name="99. Contracts for horses and mail wagons for House of Representatives.">The appropriations for hire of horses and mail wagons for carrying the mails for the House of Representatives shall be expended under the direction of the Postmaster of the House, under contracts to be let annually to the lowest responsible bidder therefor after due advertisement. (Mar. 3, 1891, c. 511, § 1, 26 Stat. 914.)</Section>
            <Section name="100. Contracts for packing boxes for House of Representatives.">Packing boxes for the use of the House of Representatives shall be procured after advertisement for proposals therefor, under specifications to be prepared by the Clerk of the House, and from the lowest and best bidder to furnish the same. (Mar. 3, 1901, c. 830, § 1, 31 Stat. 967.)</Section>
            <Section name="101. Subletting duties of employees of Senate or House of Representatives.">No employee of Congress, either in the Senate or House, shall sublet to, or hire, another to do or perform any part of the duties or work attached to the position to which he was appointed. (Mar. 2, 1895, c. 177, § 1, 28 Stat. 771.)</Section>
            <Section name="102. Statements of Secretary of Senate and Clerk of House of Representatives.">The Secretary of the Senate and the Clerk of the House of Representatives shall prepare and submit to the two Houses, respectively, at the commencement of each session of Congress, the following statements in writing: First. A statement showing the names of all the clerks and other persons who have been, during the preceding year or any part thereof, employed in their respective offices, and those of the messengers of the respective Houses; together with the time that each clerk or other person and each messenger was actually employed, and the sums paid to each. This statement must also show whether such clerks or other persons, or such messengers, have been usefully employed; whether the services of any of them can be dispensed with without detriment to the public service, and whether the removal of any particular persons, and the appointment of others in their stead, is required for the better dispatch of business. Second. A detailed statement, by items, of the manner in which the contingent fund for each House has been expended during the preceding year. This statement must give the names of every person to whom any portion of the fund has been paid; and if for anything furnished, the quantity and price; and if for any services rendered, the nature of such service, the time employed, and the particular occasion or cause, in brief, that rendered such service necessary, and the amount of all former appropriations in each case on hand, either in the Treasury or in the hands of any disbursing officer or agent. Such statements shall exhibit, also, the several sums drawn by the Secretary and Clerk, respectively, from the Treasury, and the balances, if any, remaining in their hands. (R.S. §§ 60, 61.)</Section>
            <Section name="103. Reports of subordinate disbursing officers of Senate and House of Representatives.">The Secretary of the Senate and the Clerk of the House of Representatives shall each require of the disbursing officers acting under their direction or authority, the return of precise and analytical statements and receipts for all the moneys which may have been from time to time, during the next preceding year, expended by them; and the results of such returns and the sums total shall be communicated annually to Congress, by the Secretary and Clerk, respectively. (R.S. § 62.)</Section>
            <Section name="104. Reports of all expenditures of Senate and House of Representatives.">All expenditures of the Senate and House of Representatives shall be made up to the end of each fiscal year, and shall be reported to Congress at the commencement of each regular session. (R.S. § 63.)</Section>
            <Section name="105. Preparation and contents of statement of appropriations.">The statement of all appropriations made during each session of Congress shall be prepared under the direction of the Committees on Appropriations of the Senate and House of Representatives, and said statement shall contain a chronological history of the regular appropriation bills passed during the session for which it is prepared. The statement shall indicate the amount of contracts authorized by appropriation Acts in addition to appropriations made therein, and shall also contain specific reference to all indefinite appropriations made each session and shall contain such additional information concerning estimates and appropriations as the committees may deem necessary. (R.S. § 64; Oct. 19, 1888, c. 1210, § 1, 25 Stat. 587; July 19, 1897, c. 9, § 1, 30 Stat. 130; June 7, 1924, c. 303, § 1, 43 Stat. 580.)</Section>
            <Section name="106. Stationery for Senate and House of Representatives; advertisements for.">The Secretary of the Senate and Clerk of the House of Representatives shall annually advertise, once a week for at least four weeks, in one or more of the principal papers published in the District of Columbia, for sealed proposals for supplying the Senate and House of Representatives, respectively, during the next session of Congress with the necessary stationery. The advertisement must describe the kind of stationery required, and must require the proposals to be accompanied with sufficient security for their performance. (R.S. §§ 65, 66; Feb. 18, 1875, c. 80, § 1, 18 Stat. 310.)</Section>
            <Section name="107. Same; notice of acceptance of proposals for.">All such proposals shall be kept sealed until the day specified in such advertisement for opening the same, when the same shall be opened in the presence of at least two persons, and the contract shall be given to the lowest bidder, provided he shall give satisfactory security to perform the same, under a forfeiture not exceeding double the contract price in case of failure; and in case the lowest bidder shall fail to enter into such contract and give such security, within a time to be fixed in such advertisement, then the contract shall be given to the next lowest bidder, who shall enter into such contract, and give such security. And in case of failure by the person entering into such contract to perform the same, he and his sureties shall be liable for the forfeiture specified in such contract, as liquidated damages, to be sued for in the name of the United States. (R.S. § 67; Feb. 18, 1875, c. 80, § 1, 18 Stat. 310.)</Section>
            <Section name="108. Same; contracts for separate parts of stationery.">Sections 106 and 107 of this title shall not prevent either the Secretary or the Clerk from contracting for separate parts of the supplies of stationery required to be furnished. (R.S. § 68.)</Section>
            <Section name="109. American goods to be preferred in purchases for Senate and House of Representatives.">The Secretary of the Senate and the Clerk of the House of Representatives shall, in disbursing the public moneys for the use of the two Houses, respectively, purchase only articles the growth and manufacture of the United States, provided the articles required can be procured of such growth and manufacture upon as good terms as to quality and price as are demanded for like articles of foreign growth and manufacture. (R.S. § 69.)</Section>
            <Section name="110. Purchase of paper, envelopes, etc., for stationery rooms of Senate and House of Representatives.">Paper, envelopes, and blank books required by the stationery rooms of the Senate and House of Representatives for sale to Senators and Members for official use may be purchased from the Public Printer at actual cost thereof and payment therefor shall be made before delivery. (June 5, 1920, c. 253, § 1, 41 Stat. 1030.)</Section>
            <Section name="111. Purchase of supplies for Senate and House of Representatives.">Supplies for use of the Senate and the House of Representatives may be purchased in accordance with the schedule of contract articles and prices of the General Supply Committee authorized by section 7 of Title 41. (June 5, 1920, c. 253, § 1, 41 Stat. 1030.)</Section>
            <Section name="112. Purchases of stationery and materials for folding.">Purchases of stationery and materials for folding shall be made in accordance with sections 106 to 109 of this title. All contracts and bonds for purchases made under the authority of this section shall be filed with the Committee to Audit and Control the Contingent Expenses of the Senate or the Committee on Accounts of the House of Representatives respectively. (Mar. 3, 1887, c. 392, § 1, 24 Stat. 590.)</Section>
            <Section name="113. Detailed reports of receipts and expenditures by Secretary of Senate and Clerk of House of Representatives.">The Secretary of the Senate and the Clerk of the House of Representatives, respectively, shall report to Congress on the first day of each regular session, and at the expiration of their terms of service, a full and complete statement of all their receipts and expenditures as such officers, showing in detail the items of expense, classifying them under the proper appropriations, and also showing the aggregate thereof, and exhibiting in a clear and concise manner the exact condition of all public moneys by them received, paid out, and remaining in their possession as such officers. (R.S. § 70.)</Section>
            <Section name="114. Fees for copies from Senate and House Journals.">The Secretary of the Senate and the Clerk of the House of Representatives, respectively, are entitled, for transcribing and certifying extracts from the Journal of the Senate or the executive Journal of the Senate when the injunction of secrecy has been removed, or from the Journal of the House of Representatives, except when such transcripts are required by an officer of the United States in a matter relating to the duties of his office, to receive from the persons for whom such transcripts are prepared the sum of 10 cents for each sheet containing one hundred words. (R.S. § 71.)</Section>
            <Section name="115. Index to House daily calendar.">The index to the daily calendar of business shall be printed only on Monday of each week. (Mar. 1, 1921, c. 80, § 1, 41 Stat. 1181.)</Section>
            <Section name="116. Accounts of property.">The Secretary of the Senate, the Clerk of the House of Representatives, the Sergeant-at-Arms, the Postmasters of the Senate and House of Representatives, and the Doorkeeper of the House of Representatives shall, severally, make out and return to Congress, on the first day of each regular session, and at the expiration of their respective terms of service, a full and complete account of all property belonging to the United States in their possession, respectively, at the time of returning such account. (R.S. § 72.)</Section>
            <Section name="117. Sale of waste paper.">It shall be the duty of the Clerk and Doorkeeper of the House of Representatives and the Secretary and Sergeant at Arms of the Senate to cause to be sold all waste paper and useless documents and condemned furniture that may accumulate, in their respective departments or offices, under the direction of the Committee on Accounts of their respective houses and cover the proceeds thereof into the Treasury; and they shall, at the beginning of each regular session of Congress, report to their respective Houses the amount of said sales. (Aug. 7, 1882, c. 433, § 1, 22 Stat. 337.)</Section>
            <Section name="118. Actions against officers for official acts.">In any action brought against any person for or on account of anything done by him while an officer of either House of Congress in the discharge of his official duty, in executing any order of such House, the district attorney for the district within which the action is brought, on being thereto requested by the officer sued, shall enter an appearance in behalf of such officer; and all provisions of the eighth section of the Act of July 28, 1866, entitled “An Act to protect the revenue, and for other purposes,” and also all provisions of the sections of former Acts therein referred to, so far as the same relate to the removal of suits, the withholding of executions, and the paying of judgments against revenue or other officers of the United States, shall become applicable to such action and to all proceedings and matters whatsoever connected therewith, and the defense of such action shall thenceforth be conducted under the supervision and direction of the Attorney General. (Mar. 3, 1875, c. 130, § 8, 18 Stat. 401.)</Section>
        </Chapter>
        <Chapter name="Chapter 5.—LIBRARY OF CONGRESS.">
            <Section name="131. Collections composing Library.">The Library of Congress, composed of the books, maps, and other publications which on December 1, 1873 remained in existence, from the collections theretofore united under authority of law and those added from time to time by purchase, exchange, donation, reservation from publications ordered by Congress, deposit to secure copyright, and otherwise, shall be preserved in the Library Building. The law library shall be preserved in the Capitol in the rooms which were on July 4, 1872 appropriated to its use, and in such others as may hereafter be assigned thereto. (R.S. § 80; Feb. 19, 1897, c. 205, § 1, 29 Stat. 545, 546.)</Section>
            <Section name="132. Departments of Library.">The Library of Congress shall be arranged in two departments, a general library and a law library. (R.S. § 81.)</Section>
            <Section name="133. Joint Committee during recess of Congress.">The portion of the Joint Committee of Congress upon the Library on the part of the Senate remaining in office as Senators shall during the recess of Congress exercise the powers and discharge the duties conferred by law upon the Joint Committee of Congress upon the Library. (Mar. 3, 1883, c. 141, § 2, 22 Stat. 592.)</Section>
            <Section name="134. Incidental expenses of law library.">The incidental expenses of the law library shall be paid out of the appropriations for the Library of Congress. (R.S. § 83.)</Section>
            <Section name="135. Purchase of books for law library.">The Librarian shall make the purchases of books for the law library, under the direction of and pursuant to the catalogue furnished him by the Chief Justice of the Supreme Court. (R.S. § 84.)</Section>
            <Section name="136. Librarian of Congress; appointment; bond; rules and regulations.">The Librarian of Congress shall be appointed by the President, by and with the advice and consent of the Senate. He shall, before entering upon the duties of his office, give a bond payable to the United States, in the sum of $20,000, with sureties approved by the Secretary of the Treasury, for the faithful discharge of his duties according to law, which bond shall be deposited in the office of the Secretary of the Senate. He shall make rules and regulations for the government of the Library. (R.S. § 89; Feb. 19, 1897, c. 205, § 1, 29 Stat. 544, 546.)</Section>
            <Section name="137. Use and regulation of law library.">The justices of the Supreme Court shall have free access to the law library; and they are authorized to make regulations, not inconsistent with law, for the use of the same during the sittings of the court. But such regulations shall not restrict any person authorized to take books from the Library from having access to the law library, or using the books therein in the same manner as he may be entitled to use the books of the general Library. (R.S. § 95.)</Section>
            <Section name="138. Law library open, when.">The law library shall be kept open every day so long as either House of Congress is in session. (July 11, 1888, c. 615, § 1, 25 Stat. 262.)</Section>
            <Section name="139. Report of Librarian of Congress.">The Librarian of Congress shall make to Congress at the beginning of each regular session, a report for the preceding fiscal year, as to the affairs of the Library of Congress, including the copyright business, and said report shall also include a detailed statement of all receipts and expenditures on account of the Library and said copyright business. (Feb. 19, 1897, c. 265, § 1, 29 Stat. 546.)</Section>
            <Section name="140. Employees; fitness.">All persons employed in and about said Library of Congress under the Librarian shall be appointed solely with reference to their fitness for their particular duties. (Feb. 19, 1897, c. 205, § 1, 29 Stat. 545; June 29, 1922, c. 251, § 1, 42 Stat. 715.)</Section>
            <Section name="141. Duties of Architect of the Capitol and Librarian of Congress.">The Architect of the Capitol shall have charge of all structural work at the Library Building and on the grounds, including all necessary repairs, the operation, maintenance, and repair of the mechanical plant and elevators, the care and maintenance of the grounds, and the purchasing and supplying of all furniture and equipment for the building. The employees required for the performance of the foregoing duties shall be appointed by the Architect of the Capitol. All other duties required to be performed on June 29, 1922 by the Superintendent of the Library Building and Grounds shall be performed under the direction of the Librarian of Congress, who shall appoint the employees necessary therefor. (June 29, 1922, c. 251, § 1, 42 Stat. 715.)</Section>
            <Section name="142. Office of administrative assistant and disbursing officer in Library of Congress created; appointment; duties; bond.">The position of administrative assistant and disbursing officer is created in the Library of Congress. Appointments thereto shall be made by the librarian. The administrative assistant and disbursing officer shall disburse the appropriations for the Library of Congress and the Botanic Garden and shall perform such services in connection with the duties imposed by sections 141 to 143 of this title upon the librarian as he may direct, and shall give bond payable to the United States in the sum of $30,000, with sureties approved by the Secretary of the Treasury for the faithful discharge of his duties. (June 29, 1922, c. 251, § 1, 42 Stat. 715.)</Section>
            <Section name="143. Appropriations for Library Building and Grounds.">All appropriations made to the Architect of the Capitol on account of the Library Building and Grounds shall be disbursed for that purpose in the same manner as other appropriations under his control. (June 29, 1922, c. 251, § 3, 42 Stat. 715.)</Section>
            <Section name="144. Copies of Statutes at Large.">Ten of the copies of the Statutes at Large, published by Little, Brown &amp; Co., which were deposited in the Library prior to February 5, 1859, shall be retained by the librarian for the use of the justices of the Supreme Court, during the terms of court. (R.S. § 96.)</Section>
            <Section name="145. Copies of Journals and documents.">Two copies of the Journals and Documents, and of each book printed by either House of Congress, bound as provided in section 116 of Title 44, Public Printing And Documents, shall be deposited in the Library, and must not be taken therefrom. (R.S. § 97.)</Section>
            <Section name="146. Deposit of Journals of Senate and House.">Twenty-five copies of the public Journals of the Senate and of the House of Representatives shall be deposited in the Library of the United States, at the seat of government, to be delivered to Members of Congress during any session, and to all other persons authorized by law to use the books in the Library, upon their application to the librarian, and giving their responsible receipts for the same, in like manner as for other books. (R.S. § 98.)</Section>
            <Section name="147. Bound volumes from files of House of Representatives.">The Clerk of the House of Representatives is authorized and directed to deliver to the Librarian of Congress all bound volumes of original papers, general petitions, printed matter, books, and manuscripts on June 6, 1900, in, or that may thereafter have come into or may come into, the files of the House, which in his judgment are not required to be retained in the immediate custody of the file clerk; and it shall be the duty of the Librarian of Congress to cause all such matter so delivered to him to be properly classified by Congress and arranged for preservation and ready reference. All of such matter shall be held as a part of the files of the House of Representatives, subject to its orders and rules. (June 6, 1900, c. 701, § 1, 31 Stat. 642.)</Section>
            <Section name="148. Transfer to Library of books from executive departments.">The head of any executive department or bureau or any commission of the Government is authorized from time to time to turn over to the Librarian of Congress, for the use of the Library of Congress, any books, maps, or other material in the library of the department, bureau, or commission no longer needed for its use, and in the judgment of the Librarian of Congress appropriate to the uses of the Library of Congress. (Feb. 25, 1903, c. 755, § 1, 32 Stat. 865.)</Section>
            <Section name="149. Transfer of books to other libraries.">The Librarian of Congress may from time to time transfer to other governmental libraries within the District of Columbia, including the Public Library, books and material in the possession of the Library of Congress in his judgment no longer necessary to its uses, but in the judgment of the custodians of such other collections likely to be useful to them, and may dispose of or destroy such material as has become useless. (Mar. 4, 1909, c. 297, § 1, 35 Stat. 858.)</Section>
            <Section name="150. Sale of copies of card indexes and other publications.">The Librarian of Congress Is hereby authorized to furnish to such institutions or individuals as may desire to buy them, such copies of the card indexes and other publications of the Library as may not be required for its ordinary transactions, and charge for the same a price which will cover their cost and ten per centum added; and all moneys received by him shall be deposited in the Treasury. (June 28, 1902, c. 1301, § 1, 32 Stat. 480.)</Section>
            <Section name="151. Smithsonian Library.">The library collected by the Smithsonian Institution under the provisions of the Act of August 10, 1846, chapter 25, and removed from the building of that Institution, with the consent of the Regents thereof, to the Library of Congress, shall, while there deposited, be subject to the same regulations as the Library of Congress, except as hereinafter provided. (R.S. § 99.)</Section>
            <Section name="152. Same; how kept and used.">The Smithsonian Institution shall have the use thereof in like manner as before its removal. All the books, maps, and charts of the Smithsonian Library shall be properly cared for and preserved in like manner as are those of the Congressional Library, from which the Smithsonian Library shall not be removed except on reimbursement by the Smithsonian Institution to the Treasury of the United States of expenses incurred in binding and in taking care of the same, or upon such terms and conditions as shall be mutually agreed upon by Congress and the Regents of the Institution. (R.S. § 100.)</Section>
            <Section name="153. Control of library of House of Representatives.">The library of the House of Representatives shall be under the control and direction of the Librarian of Congress, who shall provide all needful books of reference therefor. The librarian, two assistant librarians, and assistant in the library, shall be appointed by the Clerk of the House, with the approval of the Speaker of the House of Representatives. No removals shall be made from the said positions except for cause reported to and approved by the Committee on Rules. (Mar. 3, 1901, c. 830, § 1, 31 Stat. 961.)</Section>
            <Section name="154. Library of Congress Trust Fund Board; members; quorum; seal; rules and regulations.">A board Is hereby created and established, to be known as the Library of Congress Trust Fund Board (hereinafter referred to as the board), which shall consist of the Secretary of the Treasury, the chairman of the Joint Committee on the Library, the Librarian of Congress, and two persons appointed by the President for a term of five years each (the first appointments being for three and five years, respectively). Three members of the board shall constitute a quorum for the transaction of business, and the board shall have an official seal, which shall be judicially noticed. The board may adopt rules and regulations in regard to its procedure and the conduct of its business. (Mar. 3, 1925, c. 423, § 1, 43 Stat. 1107.)</Section>
            <Section name="155. Same; expenses.">No compensation shall be paid to the members of the board for their services as such members, but they shall be reimbursed for the expenses necessarily incurred by them, out of the income from the fund or funds in connection with which such expenses are incurred. The voucher of the chairman of the board shall be sufficient evidence that the expenses are properly allowable. Any expenses of the board, including the cost of its seal, not properly chargeable to the Income of any trust fund held by it, shall be estimated for in the annual estimates of the Librarian for the maintenance of the Library of Congress. (Mar. 3, 1925, c. 423, § 1, 43 Stat. 1107.)</Section>
            <Section name="156. Same; gifts, etc., to.">The board is authorized to accept, receive, hold, and administer such gifts or bequests of personal property for the benefit of, or in connection with, the Library, its collections, or its service, as may be approved by the board and by the Joint Committee on the Library. (Mar. 3, 1925, c. 423, § 1, 43 Stat. 1107.)</Section>
            <Section name="157. Same; trust funds; management of.">The moneys or securities composing the trust funds given or bequeathed to the board shall be receipted for by the Secretary of the Treasury, who shall invest, reinvest, or retain investments as the board may from time to time determine. The income as and when collected shall be deposited with the Treasurer of the United States, who shall enter it in a special account to the credit of the Library of Congress and subject to disbursement by the Librarian for the purposes in each case specified; and the Treasurer of the United States is authorized to honor the requisitions of the Librarian made in such manner and in accordance with such regulations as the Treasurer may from time to time prescribe: Provided, however, That the board is not authorized to engage in any business nor to exercise any voting privilege which may be incidental to securities in its hands, nor shall the board make any investments that could not lawfully be made by a trust company in the District of Columbia, except that it may make any investments directly authorized by the instrument of gift, and may retain any investments accepted by it. (Mar. 3, 1925, c. 423, § 1, 43 Stat. 1107.)</Section>
            <Section name="158. Same; deposits with Treasurer of United States.">Should any gift or bequest so provide, the board may deposit the principal sum, in cash, with the Treasurer of the United States as a permanent loan to the United States Treasury, and the Treasurer shall thereafter credit such deposit with interest at the rate of 4 per centum per annum, payable semiannually, such interest, as income, being subject to disbursement by the Librarian of Congress for the purposes specified: Provided, however, That the total of such principal sums at any time so held by the Treasurer under this authorization shall not exceed $5,000,000. (Mar. 3, 1925, c. 423, § 1, 43 Stat. 1107.)</Section>
            <Section name="159. Same; perpetual succession; suits by or against.">The board shall have perpetual succession, with all the usual powers and obligations of a trustee, except as herein limited, in respect of all property, moneys, or securities which shall be conveyed, transferred, assigned, bequeathed, delivered, or paid over to it for the purposes above specified. The board may be sued in the Supreme Court of the District of Columbia, which is given jurisdiction of such suits, for the purpose of enforcing the provisions of any trust accepted by it. (Mar. 3, 1925, c. 423, § 3, 43 Stat. 1108.)</Section>
            <Section name="160. Same; gifts, etc., to Library not affected.">Nothing in sections 154 to 163 of this title shall be construed as prohibiting or restricting the Librarian of Congress from accepting in the name of the United States gifts or bequests of money for immediate disbursement in the interest of the Library, its collections, or its service. Such gifts or bequests, after acceptance by the Librarian, shall be paid by the donor or his representative to the Treasurer of the United States, whose receipts shall be their acquittance. The Treasurer of the United States shall enter them in a special account to the credit of the Library of Congress and subject to disbursement by the Librarian for the purposes in each case specified. (Mar. 3, 1925, c. 423, § 4, 43 Stat. 1108.)</Section>
            <Section name="161. Same; gifts, etc., exempt from Federal taxes.">Gifts or bequests to or for the benefit of the Library of Congress, including those to the board, and the income therefrom, shall be exempt from all Federal taxes. (Mar. 3, 1925, c. 423, § 5, 43 Stat. 1108.)</Section>
            <Section name="162. Same; employees; compensation.">Employees of the Library of Congress who perform special functions for the performance of which funds have been entrusted to the board or the Librarian, or in connection with cooperative undertakings in which the Library of Congress is engaged, shall not be subject to section 70 of Title 5; nor shall any additional compensation paid to such employees be construed as a double salary under the provisions of section 63 of Title 5. (Mar. 3, 1925, c. 423, § 6, 43 Stat. 1108.)</Section>
            <Section name="163. Same; report to Congress.">The board shall submit to the Congress an annual report of the moneys or securities received and held by it and of its operations. (Mar. 3, 1925, c. 423, § 7, 43 Stat. 1108.)</Section>
        </Chapter>
        <Chapter name="Chapter 6.—CONGRESSIONAL INVESTIGATIONS.">
            <Section name="191. Oaths to witnesses.">The President of the Senate, the Speaker of the House of Representatives, or a chairman of a Committee of the Whole, or of any committee of either House of Congress, is empowered to administer oaths to witnesses in any case under their examination. Any Member of either House of Congress may administer oaths to witnesses in any matter depending in either House of Congress of which he is a Member, or any committee thereof. (R.S. § 101; June 20, 1884, c. 123, 23 Stat. 60.)</Section>
            <Section name="192. Refusal of witness to testify.">Every person who having been summoned as a witness by the authority of either House of Congress, to give testimony or to produce papers upon any matter under inquiry before either House, or any committee of either House of Congress, willfully makes default, or who, having appeared, refuses to answer any question pertinent to the question under inquiry, shall be deemed guilty of a misdemeanor, punishable by a fine of not more than $1,000 nor less than $100, and imprisonment in a common jail for not less than one month nor more than twelve months. (R.S. § 102.)</Section>
            <Section name="193. Privilege of witnesses.">No witness is privileged to refuse to testify to any fact, or to produce any paper, respecting which he shall be examined by either House of Congress, or by any committee of either House, upon the ground that his testimony to such fact or his production of such paper may tend to disgrace him or otherwise render him infamous. (R.S. § 103.)</Section>
            <Section name="194. Witnesses failing to testify.">Whenever a witness summoned as mentioned in section 192 of this title fails to testify, and the facts are reported to either House, the President of the Senate or the Speaker of the House, as the case may be, shall certify the fact under the seal of the Senate or House to the district attorney for the District of Columbia, whose duty it shall be to bring the matter before the grand jury for their action. (R.S. § 104.)</Section>
            <Section name="195. Fees of witnesses in District of Columbia.">Witnesses residing in the District of Columbia and not in the service of the government of said District or of the United States, who shall be summoned to give testimony before any committee of the House of Representatives, shall not be allowed exceeding $2 for each day’s attendance before said committee. (May 1, 1876, c. 88, 19 Stat. 41.)</Section>
        </Chapter>
        <Chapter name="Chapter 7.—CONTESTED ELECTIONS.">
            <Section name="202. Time for answer.">Any Member upon whom the notice mentioned in the preceding section may be served shall, within thirty days after the service thereof, answer such notice, admitting or denying the facts alleged therein, and stating specifically any other grounds upon which he rests the validity of his election; and shall serve a copy of his answer upon the contestant. (R.S. § 106.)</Section>
            <Section name="203. Time for taking testimony.">In all contested-election cases the time allowed for taking testimony shall be ninety days, and the testimony shall be taken in the following order: The contestant shall take testimony during the first forty days, the returned Member during the succeeding forty days, and the contestant may take testimony in rebuttal only during the remaining ten days of said period. This section shall be construed as requiring all testimony in cases of contested election to be taken within ninety days from the day on which the answer of the returned Member is served upon the contestant. (R.S. § 107; Mar. 2, 1875, c. 119, § 2, 18 Stat. 338.)</Section>
            <Section name="204. Notice of depositions; service.">The party desiring to take a deposition under the provisions of this chapter shall give the opposite party notice, in writing, of the time and place, when and where the same will be taken, of the name of the witnesses to be examined and their places of residence, and of the name of an officer before whom the same will be taken. The notice shall be personally served upon the opposite party, or upon any agent or attorney authorized by him to take testimony or cross-examine witnesses in the matter of such contest, if, by the use of reasonable diligence, such personal service can be made; but if, by the use of such diligence, personal service can not be made, the service may be made by leaving a duplicate of the notice at the usual place of abode of the opposite party. The notice shall be served so as to allow the opposite party sufficient time by the usual route of travel to attend, and one day for preparation, exclusive of Sundays and the day of service. Testimony in rebuttal may be taken on five days’ notice. (R.S. § 108.)</Section>
            <Section name="205. Testimony taken at several places at same time.">Testimony in contested-election cases may be taken at two or more places at the same time. (R.S. § 109.)</Section>
            <Section name="206. Who may issue subpoenas.">When any contestant or returned Member is desirous of obtaining testimony respecting a contested election, he may apply for a subpoena to either of the following officers who may reside within the congressional district in which the election to be contested was held: First. Any judge of any court of the United States. Second. Any chancellor, judge, or justice of a court of record of any State. Third. Any mayor, recorder, or intendant of any town or city. Fourth. Any referee in bankruptcy or notary public. (R.S. § 110; June 7, 1878, c. 160, 20 Stat. 99; July 1, 1898, c. 541, § 38, 30 Stat. 555.)</Section>
            <Section name="207. Contents of subpoena.">The officer to whom the application authorized by the preceding section is made shall thereupon issue his writ of subpoena, directed to all such witnesses as shall be named to him, requiring their attendance before him, at some time and place named in the subpoena, in order to be examined respecting the contested election. (R.S. § 111.)</Section>
            <Section name="208. When justices of the peace may act.">In case none of the officers mentioned in section 206 of this title are residing in the congressional district from which the election is proposed to be contested, the application thereby authorized may be made to any two justices of the peace residing within the district; and they may receive such application, and jointly proceed upon it. (R.S. § 112.)</Section>
            <Section name="209. Depositions by consent.">It shall be competent for the parties, their agents or attorneys authorized to act in the premises, by consent in writing, to take depositions without notice; also, by such written consent, to take depositions (whether upon or without notice) before any officer or officers authorized to take depositions in common law, or civil actions, or in chancery, by either the laws of the United States or of the State in which the same may be taken, and to waive proof of the official character of such officer or officers. Any written consent given as aforesaid shall be returned with the depositions. (R.S. § 113.)</Section>
            <Section name="210. Service of subpoena.">Each witness shall be duly served with a subpoena, by a copy thereof delivered to him or left at his usual place of abode, at least five days before the day on which the attendance of the witness is required. (R.S. § 114.)</Section>
            <Section name="211. Witnesses need not attend out of county.">No witness shall be required to attend an examination out of the county in which he may reside or be served with a subpoena. (R.S. § 115.)</Section>
            <Section name="212. Penalty for failure to attend or testify.">Any person who, having been summoned in the manner above directed, refuses or neglects to attend and testify, unless prevented by sickness or unavoidable necessity, shall forfeit the sum of $20, to be recovered, with costs of suit, by the party at whose instance the subpoena was issued, and for his use, by an action of debt, to any court of the United States, and shall also be liable to indictment for a misdemeanor, and punishment by fine and imprisonment. (R.S. § 116.)</Section>
            <Section name="213. Witnesses outside of district.">Depositions of witnesses residing outside of the district and beyond the reach of a subpoena may be taken before any officer authorized by law to take testimony in contested-election cases in the district in which the witness to be examined may reside. (R.S. § 117.)</Section>
            <Section name="214. Party notified may select officer.">The party notified as aforesaid, his agent or attorney, may, if he see fit, select an officer (having authority to take depositions in such cases) to officiate, with the officer named in the notice, in the taking of the depositions; and if both such officers attend, the depositions shall be taken before them both, sitting together, and be certified by them both. But if only one of such officers attend, the depositions may be taken before and certified by him alone. (R.S. § 118.)</Section>
            <Section name="215. Depositions taken by party or agent.">At the taking of any deposition under this chapter, either party may appear and act in person, or by agent or attorney. (R.S. § 119.)</Section>
            <Section name="216. Examination of witnesses.">All witnesses who attend in obedience to a subpoena, or who attend voluntarily at the time and place appointed, of whose examination notice has been given, as provided by this chapter, shall then and there be examined on oath by the officer who issued the subpoena, or, in case of his absence, by any other officer who is authorized to issue such subpoena, or by the officer before whom the depositions are to be taken by written consent, or before whom the depositions of witnesses residing outside of the district are to be taken as the case may be, touching all such matters respecting the election about to be contested as shall be proposed by either of the parties or their agents. (R.S. § 120.)</Section>
            <Section name="217. Testimony, to what confined.">The testimony to be taken by either party to the contest shall be confined to the proof or disproof of the facts alleged or denied in the notice and answer mentioned in sections 201 and 202 of this title. (R.S. § 121.)</Section>
            <Section name="218. Testimony, written out and attested.">The officer shall cause the testimony of the witnesses, together with the questions proposed by the parties or their agents, to be reduced to writing in his presence, and in the presence of the parties or their agents, if attending, and to be duly attested by the witnesses respectively. (R.S. § 122.)</Section>
            <Section name="219. Production of papers.">The officer shall have power to require the production of papers; and on the refusal or neglect of any person to produce and deliver up any paper or papers in his possession pertaining to the election, or to produce and deliver up certified or sworn copies of the same in case they may be official papers, such person shall be liable to all the penalties prescribed in section 212 of this title. All papers thus produced, and all certified or sworn copies of official papers, shall be transmitted by the officer, with the testimony of the witnesses, to the Clerk of the House of Representatives. (R.S. § 123.)</Section>
            <Section name="220. Adjournments.">The taking of the testimony may, if so stated in the notice, be adjourned from day to day. (R.S. § 124.)</Section>
            <Section name="221. Notice attached to depositions.">The notice to take depositions, with the proof or acknowledgment of the service thereof, and a copy of the subpoena, where any has been served, shall be attached to the depositions when completed. (R.S. § 125.)</Section>
            <Section name="222. Copy of notice and answer to accompany testimony.">A copy of the notice of contest, and of the answer of the returned Member, shall be prefixed to the depositions taken, and transmitted with them to the Clerk of the House of Representatives. (R.S. § 126.)</Section>
            <Section name="223. Testimony sent to Clerk of House of Representatives; printing testimony; briefs.">All officers taking testimony to be used in a contested-election case, whether by deposition or otherwise, shall, when the taking of the same is completed, and without unnecessary delay, certify and carefully seal and immediately forward the same, by mail or by express, addressed to the Clerk of the House of Representatives of the United States, Washington, District of Columbia; and shall also indorse upon the envelope containing such deposition or testimony the name of the case in which it is taken, together with the name of the party in whose behalf it is taken, and shall subscribe such indorsement. The Clerk of the House of Representatives, upon the receipt of such deposition or testimony, shall notify the contestant and the contested, by registered letter through the mails, to appear before him at the Capitol, in person or by attorney, at a reasonable time to be named, not exceeding twenty days from the mailing of such letter, for the purpose of being present at the opening of the sealed packages of testimony and of agreeing upon the parts thereof to be printed. Upon the day appointed for such meeting the said Clerk shall proceed to open all the packages of testimony in the case, in the presence of the parties or their attorneys, and such portions of the testimony as the parties may agree to have printed shall be printed by the Public Printer, under the direction of the said Clerk; and in case of disagreement between the parties as to the printing of any portion of the testimony, the said Clerk shall determine whether such portion of the testimony shall be printed; and the said Clerk shall prepare a suitable index to be printed with the record. And the notice of contest and the answer of the sitting Member shall also be printed with the record. If either party, after having been duly notified, should fail to attend, by himself or by an attorney, the Clerk shall proceed to open the packages, and shall cause such portions of the testimony to be printed, as he shall determine. He shall carefully seal up and preserve the portions of the testimony not printed, as well as the other portions when returned from the Public Printer, and lay the same before the Committee on Elections at the earliest opportunity. As soon as the testimony in any case is printed the Clerk shall forward by mail, if desired, two copies thereof to the contestant and the same number to the contested; and shall notify the contestant to file with the Clerk, within thirty days, a brief of the facts and the authorities relied on to establish his case. The Clerk shall forward by mail two copies of the contestant's brief to the contested, with like notice. Upon receipt of the contested's brief the Clerk shall forward two copies thereof to the contestant, who may, if he desires, reply to new matter in the contested's brief within like time. All briefs shall be printed at the expense of the parties respectively, and shall be of like folio as the printed record; and sixty copies thereof shall be filed with the Clerk for the use of the Committee on Elections. (R.S. § 127; Mar. 2, 1875, c. 119, § 1, 18 Stat. 338; Mar. 2, 1887, c. 318, 24 Stat. 445.)</Section>
            <Section name="224. Fees of witnesses.">Every witness attending by virtue of any subpoena herein directed to be issued shall be entitled to receive the sum of 75 cents for each day’s attendance, and the further sum of 5 cents for every mile necessarily traveled in going and returning. Such allowance shall be ascertained and certified by the officer taking the examination, and shall be paid by the party at whose instance such witness was summoned. (R.S. § 128.)</Section>
            <Section name="225. Fees of officers.">Each judge, justice, chancellor, chief executive officer of a town or city, referee in bankruptcy, notary public, and justice of the peace, who shall be necessarily employed pursuant to the provisions of this chapter, and all sheriffs, constables, or other officers who may be employed to serve any subpoena or notice herein authorized, shall be entitled to receive from the party at whose instance the service shall have been performed such fees as are allowed for similar services in the State wherein such service may be rendered. (R.S. § 129.)</Section>
            <Section name="226. Limitation of expenses of contest for seat in House.">No contestee or contestant for a seat in the House of Representatives shall be paid exceeding $2,000 for expenses in election contests; and before any sum whatever shall be paid to a contestant or contestee for expenses of election contest, he shall file with the clerk of the Committee on Elections a full and detailed account of his expenses, accompanied by the vouchers and receipts for each item, which account and vouchers shall be sworn to by the party presenting the same, and no charges for witness fees shall be allowed in said accounts unless made in strict conformity to section 224 of this title. (R.S. § 130; Mar. 3, 1879, c. 182, § 1, 20 Stat. 400.)</Section>
        </Chapter>
        <Chapter name="Chapter 8.—FEDERAL CORRUPT PRACTICES.">
            <Section name="242. Chairman and treasurer of political committee; duties as to contributions; accounts and receipts.">(a) Every political committee shall have a chairman and a treasurer. No contribution shall be accepted, and no expenditure made, by or on behalf of a political committee for the purpose of influencing an election until such chairman and treasurer have been chosen.(b) It shall be the duty of the treasurer of a political committee to keep a detailed and exact account of:(1) All contributions made to or for such committee;(2) The name and address of every person making any such contribution, and the date thereof;(3) All expenditures made by or on behalf of such committee; and(4) The name and address of every person to whom any such expenditure is made, and the date thereof.(c) It shall be the duty of the treasurer to obtain and keep a receipted bill, stating the particulars, for every expenditure by or on behalf of a political committee exceeding $10 in amount. The treasurer shall preserve all receipted bills and accounts required to be kept by this section for a period of at least two years from the date of the filing of the statement containing such items. (June 25, 1910, c. 392, §§ 2, 3, 36 Stat. 823; Feb. 28, 1925, c. 368, Title III, § 303, 43 Stat. 1071.)</Section>
            <Section name="243. Accounts of contributions received.">Every person who receives a contribution for a political committee shall, on demand of the treasurer, and in any event within five days after the receipt of such contribution, render to the treasurer a detailed account thereof, including the name and address of the person making such contribution, and the date on which received. (June 25, 1910, c. 392, § 4, 36 Stat. 823; Feb. 28, 1925, c. 368, Title III, § 304, 43 Stat. 1071.)</Section>
            <Section name="244. Statements by treasurer filed with Clerk of House of Representatives.">(a) The treasurer of a political committee shall file with the Clerk between the 1st and 10th days of March, June, and September in each year, and also between the 10th and 15th days, and on the 5th day next preceding the date on which a general election is to be held, at which candidates are to be elected in two or more States, and also on the 1st day of January, a statement containing, complete as of the day next preceding the date of filing:(1) The name and address of each person who has made a contribution to or for such committee in one or more items of the aggregate amount or value, within the calendar year, of $100 or more, together with the amount and date of such contribution;(2) The total sum of the contributions made to or for such committee during the calendar year and not stated under paragraph (1);(3) The total sum of all contributions made to or for such committee during the calendar year;(4) The name and address of each person to whom an expenditure in one or more items of the aggregate amount or value, within the calendar year, of $10 or more has been made by or on behalf of such committee, and the amount, date, and purpose of such expenditure;(5) The total sum of all expenditures made by or on behalf of such committee during the calendar year and not stated under paragraph (4);(6) The total sum of expenditures made by or on behalf of such committee during the calendar year.(b) The statements required to be filed by subdivision (a) shall be cumulative during the calendar year to which they relate, but where there has been no change in an item reported in a previous statement only the amount need be carried forward.(c) The statement filed on the 1st day of January shall cover the preceding calendar year. (June 25, 1910, c. 392, §§ 5, 6, 36 Stat. 823; Aug. 19, 1911, c. 33, § 1, 37 Stat. 25; Feb. 28, 1925, c. 368, Title III, § 305, 43 Stat. 1071.)</Section>
            <Section name="245. Statements by others than political committee filed with Clerk of House of Representatives.">Every person (other than a political committee) who makes an expenditure in one or more items, other than by contribution to a political committee, aggregating $50 or more within a calendar year for the purpose of influencing in two or more States the election of candidates, shall file with the Clerk an itemized detailed statement of such expenditure in the same manner as required of the treasurer of a political committee by section 244 of this title. (June 25, 1910, c. 392, § 7, 36 Stat. 824; Feb. 28, 1925, c. 368, Title III, § 306, 43 Stat. 1072.)</Section>
            <Section name="246. Statements by candidates for Senator, Representative, Delegate, or Resident Commissioner filed with Secretary of Senate and Clerk of House of Representatives.">(a) Every candidate for Senator shall file with the Secretary, and every candidate for Representative, Delegate, or Resident Commissioner shall file with the Clerk, not less than ten nor more than fifteen days before, and within thirty days after, the date on which an election is to be held, a statement containing, complete as of the day next preceding the date of filing:(1) A correct and itemized account of each contribution received by him or by any person for him with his knowledge or consent, from any source, in aid or support of his candidacy for election, or for the purpose of influencing the result of the election, together with the name of the person who has made such contribution;(2) A correct and itemized account of each expenditure made by him or by any person for him with his knowledge or consent, in aid or support of his candidacy for election, or for the purpose of influencing the result of the election, together with the name of the person to whom such expenditure was made; except that only the total sum of expenditures for items specified in subdivision (c) of section 248 of this title need be stated;(3) A statement of every promise or pledge made by him or by any person for him with his consent, prior to the closing of the polls on the day of the election, relative to the appointment or recommendation for appointment of any person to any public or private position or employment for the purpose of procuring support in his candidacy, and the name, address, and occupation of every person to whom any such promise or pledge has been made, together with the description of any such position. If no such promise or pledge has been made, that fact shall be specifically stated. (b) The statements required to be filed by subdivision (a) shall be cumulative, but where there has been no change in an item reported in a previous statement only the amount need be carried forward. (c) Every candidate shall inclose with his first statement a report, based upon the records of the proper State official, stating the total number of votes cast for all candidates for the office which the candidate seeks, at the general election next preceding the election at which he is a candidate. (June 25, 1910, c. 392, § 8, 36 Stat. 824; Aug. 19, 1911, c. 33, § 2, 37 Stat. 26; Aug. 23, 1912, c. 349, 37 Stat. 360; Feb. 28, 1925, c. 368, Title III, § 307, 43 Stat. 1072.)</Section>
            <Section name="247. Statements; Verification; Filing; Preservation; Inspection.">A statement required by this chapter to be filed by a candidate or treasurer of a political committee or other person with the Clerk or Secretary, as the case may be:(a) Shall be verified by the oath or affirmation of the person filing such statement, taken before any officer authorized to administer oaths;(b) Shall be deemed properly filed when deposited in an established post office within the prescribed time, duly stamped, registered, and directed to the Clerk or Secretary at Washington, District of Columbia, but in the event it is not received, a duplicate of such statement shall be promptly filed upon notice by the Clerk or Secretary of its nonreceipt;(c) Shall be preserved by the Clerk or Secretary for a period of two years from the date of filing, shall constitute a part of the public records of his office, and shall be open to public inspection. (June 25, 1910, c. 392, § 8, 36 Stat. 824; Aug. 19, 1911, c. 33, § 2, 37 Stat. 26; Aug. 23, 1912, c. 349, 37 Stat. 360; Feb. 28, 1925, c. 368, Title III, § 308, 43 Stat. 1072.)</Section>
            <Section name="248. Limitation upon amount of expenditures by Candidate.">(a) A candidate, in his campaign for election, shall not make expenditures in excess of the amount which he may lawfully make under the laws of the State in which he is a candidate, nor in excess of the amount which he may lawfully make under the provisions of this title. (b) Unless the laws of his State prescribe a less amount as the maximum limit of campaign expenditures, a candidate may make expenditures up to: (1) The sum of $10,000 if a candidate for Senator, or the sum of $2,500 if a candidate for Representative, Delegate, or Resident Commissioner; or (2) An amount equal to the amount obtained by multiplying three cents by the total number of votes cast at the last general election for all candidates for the office which the candidate seeks, but in no event exceeding $25,000 if a candidate for Senator or $5,000 if a candidate for Representative, Delegate, or Resident Commissioner. (c) Money expended by a candidate to meet and discharge any assessment, fee, or charge made or levied upon candidates by the laws of the State in which he resides, or expended for his necessary personal, traveling, or subsistence expenses, or for stationery, postage, writing, or printing (other than for use on billboards or in newspapers), for distributing letters, circulars, or posters, or for telegraph or telephone service, shall not be included in determining whether his expenditures have exceeded the sum fixed by paragraph (1) or (2) of subdivision (b) as the limit of campaign expenses of a candidate. (June 25, 1910, c. 392, §§ 8, 9, 36 Stat. 824; Aug. 19, 1911, c. 33, § 2, 37 Stat. 26; Aug. 23, 1912, c. 349, 37 Stat. 360; Feb. 28, 1925, c. 368, Title III, § 309, 43 Stat. 1073.)</Section>
            <Section name="249. Promises or pledges by candidate.">It is unlawful for any candidate to directly or indirectly promise or pledge the appointment, or the use of his influence or support for the appointment of any person to any public or private position or employment, for the purpose of procuring support in his candidacy. (June 25, 1910, c. 392, § 8, 36 Stat. 824; Aug. 19, 1911, c. 33, § 2, 37 Stat. 26; Aug. 23, 1912, c. 349, 37 Stat. 360; Feb. 28, 1925, c. 368, Title III, § 310, 43 Stat. 1073.)</Section>
            <Section name="250. Expenditures to influence voting.">It is unlawful for any person to make or offer to make an expenditure, or to cause an expenditure to be made or offered, to any person, either to vote or withhold his vote, or to vote for or against any candidate, and it is unlawful for any person to solicit, accept, or receive any such expenditure in consideration of his vote or the withholding of his vote. (June 25, 1910, c. 392, § 8, 36 Stat. 824; Aug. 19, 1911, c. 33, § 2, 37 Stat. 26; Aug. 23, 1912, c. 349, 37 Stat. 360; Feb. 28, 1925, c. 368, Title III, § 311, 43 Stat. 1073.)</Section>
            <Section name="251. Contributions by national banks or other Federal corporations; penalty.">It is unlawful for any national bank, or any corporation organized by authority of any law of Congress, to make a contribution in connection with any election to any political office, or for any corporation whatever to make a contribution in connection with any election at which presidential and vice presidential electors or a Senator or Representative in, or a Delegate or Resident Commissioner to, Congress are to be voted for, or for any candidate, political committee, or other person to accept or receive any contribution prohibited by this section. Every corporation which makes any contribution in violation of this section shall be fined not more than $5,000; and every officer or director of any corporation who consents to any contribution by the corporation in violation of this section shall be fined not more than $5,000; and every officer or director of any corporation who consents to any contribution by the corporation in violation of this section shall be fined not more than $1,000, or imprisoned not more than one year, or both. (Jan. 26, 1907, c. 420, 34 Stat. 864; Mar. 4, 1909, c. 321, § 83, 35 Stat. 1103; Feb. 28, 1925, c. 368, Title III, § 313, 43 Stat. 1074.)</Section>
            <Section name="252. General penalties for violations.">(a) Any person who violates any of the foregoing provisions of this chapter, except those for which a specific penalty is imposed by section 208 of Title 18, and section 251 of this title, shall be fined not more than $1,000 or imprisoned not more than one year, or both. (b) Any person who willfully violates any of the foregoing provisions of this chapter, except those for which a specific penalty is imposed by section 208 of Title 18, and section 251 of this title, shall be fined not more than $10,000 and imprisoned not more than two years. (June 25, 1910, c. 392, § 11, 36 Stat. 824; Aug. 19, 1911, c. 33, § 2, 37 Stat. 26; Feb. 28, 1925, c. 368, Title III, § 314, 43 Stat. 1074.)</Section>
            <Section name="253. Expenses of election contests.">This chapter shall not limit or affect the right of any person to make expenditures for proper legal expenses in contesting the results of an election. (June 25, 1910, c. 392, § 10, 36 Stat. 824; Aug. 19, 1911, c. 33, § 2, 37 Stat. 26; Feb. 28, 1925, c. 368, Title III, § 315, 43 Stat. 1074.)</Section>
            <Section name="254. State laws not affected.">This chapter shall not be construed to annul the laws of any State relating to the nomination or election of candidates, unless directly inconsistent with the provisions of this title, or to exempt any candidate from complying with such State laws. (June 25, 1910, c. 392, § 8, 36 Stat. 824; Aug. 19, 1911, c. 33, § 2, 37 Stat. 26; Aug. 23, 1912, c. 349, 37 Stat. 300; Feb. 28, 1925, c. 368, Title III, § 316, 43 Stat. 1074.)</Section>
            <Section name="255. Partial invalidity.">If any provision of this chapter or the application thereof to any person or circumstance is held invalid, the validity of the remainder of the chapter and of the application of such provision to other persons and circumstances shall not be affected thereby. (Feb. 28, 1925, c. 368, Title III, § 317, 43 Stat. 1074.)</Section>
            <Section name="256. Citation.">This chapter may be cited as the “Federal Corrupt Practices Act.” (Feb. 28, 1925, c. 368, Title III, § 301, 43 Stat. 1070.)</Section>
        </Chapter>
        <Chapter name="Chapter 9.—OFFICE OF LEGISLATIVE COUNSEL.">
            <Section name="272. Appointment of legislative counsel; qualifications.">One of the legislative counsel shall be appointed by the President of the Senate, and one by the Speaker of the House of Representatives, without reference to political affiliations and solely on the ground of fitness to perform the duties of the office. (Feb. 24, 1919, c. 18, § 1303, 40 Stat. 1111 ; June 2, 1921, c. 234, § 1101, 43 Stat. 353.)</Section>
            <Section name="273. Compensation of legislative counsel.">The positions of legislative counsel shall be allocated from time to time by the President of the Senate and the Speaker of the House of Representatives, jointly, to the appropriate grade in the compensation schedules of section 673 of Title 5. The rate of compensation of each of the two legislative counsel shall be fixed from time to time, within the limits of such grade, by the President of the Senate and the Speaker of the House of Representatives, respectively. (June 2, 1924, c. 234, § 1101, 43 Stat. 353.)</Section>
            <Section name="274. Assistant legislative counsel; clerks and employees; office equipment and supplies.">The legislative counsel shall, subject to the approval of the President of the Senate and the Speaker of the House of Representatives, employ and fix the compensation of such assistant counsel, clerks, and other employees, and purchase such furniture, office equipment, books, stationery, and other supplies, as may be necessary for the proper performance of the duties of the office and as may be appropriated for by Congress. (Feb. 24, 1919, c. 18. § 1303, 40 Stat. 1141; June 2, 1924, c. 234, § 1101, 43 Stat. 338.)</Section>
            <Section name="275. Duties of office; rules and regulations.">The Office of the Legislative Counsel shall aid in drafting public bills and resolutions or amendments thereto on the request of any committee of either House of Congress, but the Library Committee of the Senate and the Library Committee of the House of Representatives, respectively, may determine the preference, if any, to be given to such requests of the committees of either House, respectively. The legislative counsel shall, from time to time, prescribe rules and regulations for the conduct of the work of the office for the committees of each House, subject to the approval of the Library Committee of each House, respectively. (Feb. 24, 1919, c. 18, § 1303, 40 Stat. 1141; June 2, 1924, c. 234, § 1101, 43 Stat. 353.)</Section>
            <Section name="276. Disbursement of appropriations.">One-half of all appropriations for the office shall be disbursed by the Secretary of the Senate and one-half by the Clerk of the House of Representatives. (Feb. 24, 1919, c. 18, § 1303, 40 Stat. 1144 ; June 2, 1924, c. 234, § 1101, 43 Stat. 353.)</Section>
            <Section name="277. Official mail matter.">The legislative counsel shall have the same privilege of free transmission of official mail matter as other officers of the United States Government. (June 2, 1924, c. 234, § 1101, 43 Stat. 353.)</Section>
        </Chapter>
    </Title>
</USCode>